leapfile.com 2005-12-12

# Email Large Files Send Large Files - Web File Transfer System

LeapFILE has established this Privacy Policy because your privacy is extremely important to us.  You provide us with personal information that you expect will be kept confidential.  Any personal information that you may provide to us will be used to provide you, our customer, better information, products and services. 

This policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.  Please read the complete Privacy Policy, as this Policy applies to anyone who uses this web site worldwide.  We may need to revise our Privacy Policy at times, and suggest that you revisit this page frequently to review the most current Privacy Policy. 

### Information Collection 

There are places on our site where we may ask for personal information that uniquely identifies you.  At times we may request information, however, fields are not normally required unless they are explicitly stated.  Personal information may include but is not limited to your first and last name, company, email address, bill to address, ship to address, phone number, fax number, credit card number and credit card expiration date. 

### Use of Personal Information 

Personal information may be used in any of the following ways:  To ensure that the content, products and services found on our site are relevant and helpful for you, to fulfill your orders for services, to notify you of special promotions, service upgrades, and other updated information about our company, and to send you other information that you may have requested from us, such as email newsletters. 

Your information will be stored in the United States.  LeapFILE may disclose your personal information to federal, state and local government officials in the United States or other countries if required to do so by law. 

### Control & Access to Personal Information 

You may find out how much personal information we have about you at any time by requesting that information from LeapFILE.  You may change any of your personal information at any time or request to be removed from our mailing list by sending an email to [support@leapfile.com](mailto:announce@nsoftware.com). 

### Security 

Your personal information is held on limited access servers LeapFILE.  We take reasonable steps to protect the personal information provided to us from unauthorized access and disclosure. 

### Use of Cookies 

LeapFILE uses cookies to ensure that the content we publish on our site is what our customers need and want.  Cookies are small text files that are used to identify users as they access information throughout our site.  When someone enters our web site, a cookie is placed on their machine (only if the person accepts cookies) or is read if the person has previously visited our web site.

Our cookies do not track or collect any personal information.  They are used to provide our customers with the most useful information through understanding what areas of our site receive the most traffic and interest. 

If you choose to disable cookies on your computer browser, you may not be able to fully access all of the products or services found on our site. 

### Third Party Services 

LeapFILE's web site contains links to other sites on the Internet.  We do not share your personal information with those sites, nor are we responsible for the content on their web sites.

We may provide personal information to third-party service providers that aid us in the delivery of products and/or services. LeapFILE does not disclose information to any third-party that is not legally obligated to protect your personal information.  LeapFILE does not sell your personal information collected online without your explicit consent. 

### Children 

Our web site does not target nor is it intended to attract children under 13 years old. LeapFILE does not knowingly solicit, collect, or accept personal information from children under 13 years of age. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy 

LeapFILE will occasionally change and update this Privacy Policy.  Any changes made to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this site.  If we make any substantial changes in our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this site. 

### Questions or Suggestions 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at legal@leapfile.com.
